♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
I don't like Uno that way.
[Denden] So, Gavin is really your bet?
[in English] So, you're dumping me?!
I think it's not fair to you
to enter a relationship
where the guy is already
half-hearted with you.
So, it is Karla then?
[Cathy] Just be together.
Your new mission.
Rizaldo Coloma, the mayor who's in hiding?
[in English] The corrupt mayor,
bagman of senators.
[Mercado] You need to find him.
[all cheering] Atoy! Atoy!
[Red] That's your biggest mistake, Atoy.
You showed yourself to me.
[Emerson]
So, now you're the real daughter.
All of it!
- [Ibyang] The bullying Janine did to me.
- [Emerson] Bullying.
I'll do the same to her!
[cackles]
Just kidding!
Don't move too much.
- Hi, Father! Ah, hello.
- Oh? Come on, eat.
So, you're hiding here.
That means Audrey is here too.
Oh, there.
That insect on your face is gone.
Yes, like a green firefly
that keeps moving.
[Father Peping] You didn't feel it?
Where are you going?
[Ibyang] Let's not fight anymore, okay?
[Atoy] Didn't you see anyone else
here earlier?
It's like someone tried to kill me, eh.
[Paldo] This belongs to Red.
- I remember he used this before.
- [Janine, in English] Uncle Red?
[groans]
- [Kurt] Ibyang and Janine,
- [in English] Get your filthy hands…
- they've been taken.
- [groans]
They were loaded into a black
SUV by a bald guy!
[in English] It's Red.
Where are the kids? Ibyang? Janine?
- They were abducted by Red.
- What?!
Do you know where your parents
might have taken the kids?
[Gavin] I don't know, Brother Atoy.
Red!
[Audrey, in English]
Red, where the hell are my daughters?!
Where are the kids?
Give me back the children!
I'll make these kids suffer.
I'll profit from them.
[Red on the phone] I'll send you pictures.
So you'll know where they're going.
And what condition they're in.
No, no, no, no! Hello! No!
PREVIOUSLY
What do we do?
Call him.
He's not answering.
- [theme music fades]
- [Jona] Brother Kurt, are you okay?
- [man] You were hit hard.
- [Jona] That kick earlier was intense, eh.
[indistinct chatter]
Excuse me! It's heavy, heavy!
Oh! Skin and bones,
gone right away! [chuckles]
We already gave away all the food,
it's done.
Ah, what's happening?
Is there trouble here again?
Ibyang and Janine were abducted
by… by Red Regalia.
What?! [gasps]
[Gavin] Karla!
[pensive music playing]
Your mother's been looking for you!
Do you know Janine and Ibyang are missing?
Eh, fool, they just told me, oh!
Eh, why does it sound like
you're blaming me?
Of course, I'm worried about you!
We! We're worried about you!
There's a kidnapping happening,
and you're still wandering around.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're a Regalia, right?
Jona, this is Red's child, right?
[heavy music playing]
That's right!
Yes, him!
[Siony] Ahh!
You don't know what your father did?!
Or maybe you're your father's spy?
[Jona] Truth!
Boy, you're banned here!
Your father is evil!
- [Jona] True! Right! Right, he's evil!
- [man] Get out! Yes!
[Nestor] Hey, Tisoy.
Aren't you going to do anything?
I don't know anything. I'm not--
- I'm not involved in that.
- Oh.
I already left our house.
Bring back the children!
- [Siony] Yes.
- Where did you take them?!
Your father is a demon!
[Jona] Right! Demon!
- Yes! Your father is a demon!
- The children. My God!
[Karla] Wait.
Gavin didn't do anything wrong!
No, Karla!
Maybe if we lock him up,
they'll return the children!
Exchange of heads!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Just wait!
Just wait!
Gavin didn't do anything wrong.
In fact, he was with us when we rescued
Brother Atoy at the junkyard!
[tense music playing]
That's the truth.
[music fades]
So, they escaped.
[theme music playing]
[music swells]
[music fades]
Why did my parents turn out like that?
[pensive music playing]
[sighs] Sorry.
Gavin…
Good thing you didn't take after
your parents.
But let's focus first. We need…
We need to know
where they could have taken the children.
Aunt Audrey, what if I just go home?
So, I can get close to Dad or even Mom!
Maybe I can get info
on where they took Ibyang and Janine!
No! I won't allow it, Gavin!
Red is no longer in his right mind!
He killed your grandfather!
There's nothing he can't do!
[in English] You're not going anywhere.
[suspicious music playing]
That's right. Gavin… they'll suspect more
if you do that. Right.
Maybe we'll find something in their house.
[in English] Documents…
Old property files.
Auntie, didn't you say you saw your dad's
human trafficking files?
Maybe you'll remember a clue there.
It's like…
Ah, I think I saw something, uhm…
[in English] Uhm, V-- V. Starts with a V.
Ve…
Ve-- Velora Bay!
[Audrey] Ve-- Velora Bay!
[tense music playing]
I can't find anything here.
[Lily] Wait.
- I can't find anything.
- Wait, wait.
[Atoy] Isn't there anything else?
Velora Bay, Velora Bay,
Velora Bay, Velora Bay.
Wait, wait. I think I saw that
on the laptop.
- [Uno] There's something?
- Wait.
Right, it's in--
it's in the classified data!
I need the laptop.
[Uno] All right.
[music fades]
[suspicious music playing]
I asked Father Peping to hide this laptop
here before I went on the mission.
I'm sure, if things get tight…
they'll search my house for it.
Only the two of us know about this.
Thank you very much for keeping it safe.
[sighs]
Complete?
- [music swells]
- [keyboard clacking]
[in English] There. This is the location.
- [ominous music playing]
- [Atoy] That's a huge place, ah.
Where is that?
[Lily]
It's posing as a high-end beach resort,
but it's actually one of the big
concentration camps
of the terrorist group Obsidian.
They're also connected
to the Black Meridian group.
[Atoy, in English] Black Meridian.
That's the international
human trafficking syndicate.
[Lily, in English] Yeah. One and only.
It's hard to get in here.
[in English]
The island is heavily guarded.
They have state-of-the-art radar systems,
because of their large involvement
in illegal activities.
So, no one gets in
without being detected by the sensors.
[in English] Whether by air or underwater.
So, what now?
If they were taken there, what do we do?
How do we get them out?!
[tense music playing]
No matter what happens,
I'll get our children back.
If this has to be my last mission,
I'll do it.
What matters, Atoy…
is that you bring the children
back safely.
[music fades]
Who owns that island?
[heavy music playing]
[Mercado, in English]
That is Mr. Edison Kalaf.
The owner of Velora Bay.
He owns multiple businesses
across the Philippines.
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] Big time!
Where is this?
[in English] According to our intel…
he has a club here that he often visits
at this time of the year.
Where is this club?
- I want to go there.
- [chuckles]
Well, it's not your ordinary club.
It's in Ermita.
It's different.
[cool upbeat music playing]
[Atoy, in English] Ah, beer for all!
Oh, no. Sorry, uh…
[Atoy] Mister Nestor can't.
Just juice, just one.
And, uh… chicharon bulaklak.
[Gavin ordering]
Sisig, sisig.
Sisig, sisig, sisig.
[indistinct chatter]
- [Paldo] Thank you.
- [Emerson] And, what else-- no.
[indistinct chatter]
[applauding]
[in English] Well, hello, hello!
Hi! And good evening!
Good evening
to all our guests for tonight!
[Trinity, in English]
Did you guys enjoy that one?
Yes! Amazing, isn't it?
[cheering]
All right!
But you'll surely enjoy
our upcoming event more--
The Reyna Royale Rumble!
[cheering]
[Trinity, in English] To our regulars,
you already know what this is.
Because we do this annually.
[chuckles]
Oh, right?
But to our newcomers,
I see a lot of newcomers.
Yes.
This is a special event.
Okay, where groups will battle
in drag performances,
[Trinity] consisting of five to six
beautiful drag queens.
- [man whoops]
- [cheering]
[Trinity] Here's the catch!
The winning group will win one million
in cash!
[cheering]
And an all-expense paid trip to Europe!
[in English] But!
Not only that, not only that.
The winners will be invited to perform…
at Mr. Edison Kalaf's 60th birthday bash.
[cheering]
On his private, members-only island, oh.
At Velora Bay!
[cheering]
- [Trinity] Right?
- [cheering]
That's my boss.
I mean, he owns this club, so he's rich.
[Trinity, in English]
So, what are you guys waiting for?
If you want to join,
this is the last day to register.
So, whoever wants to join, go, go, go!
[cheering]
Let's go, girls! Come on!
[Trinity] Let's party!
[cheering]
Hey, hey! Come on!
What's attached to them, what is that, eh?
Like it's just fake…
[Paldo] I think so too.
[upbeat music playing]
[chuckles]
Why are you looking at me like that, 'Toy?
Do you know how to dance?
Dance? Like this?
Sit down.
We might get accused of something--
[Emerson] What, back in…
back in high school, the Tinikling.
The Pandanggo sa Ilaw, the Tinik--
No, not in the program.
Not school program.
That's all, when I was in school.
Ah, ah-- Atoy, I did ballet.
Ah, in grade three, I did ballet.
But I got injured,
so I stopped in grade four. There.
Big brother, I do hip-hop.
- Hip-hop?
- [Gavin] Does that work?
- [cool upbeat music playing]
- [clears throat]
'Toy.
Why, 'Toy? What are you planning?
[Trinity, in English]
Come on! Let's party!
[audience cheering]
[Trinity] Hey, hey! Come on! Come on!
Hey, hey! Get up! Come on!
Feel beautiful, feel beautiful! Get up!
[music fades]
Do your best, huh.
[in English] I'm rooting for you, Queen.
- Thank you, Queen.
- [drag queen] Good luck.
[indistinct chatter]
- So? Do you have a dress?
- No!
- That won't work, 'Day.
- Lend me a dress.
[indistinct chatter]
[drag queen] Oh, let's go in.
[grunts]
We got number seven.
So, that means
we still have a few days to prepare.
Huh? What--
Ah, ah--
Ah, A-- Atoy, you mean we'll…
we'll dress up as drag queens?
Yes. That's it, we'll copy them.
We'll perform.
But we need to go all out.
Really all out so we'll win. That's it.
[Gavin] I think I'll pass.
[sneaky music playing]
- What?
- Are you sure about that, Atoy?
Yes!
So, are you game?
- [clears throat]
- Keribels or witchikels?
What's that? What are you saying?
Keribels, I heard it earlier.
"Keribels" means yes. We're game.
"Witchikels" means no.
So? Keri? It should be keribels!
Uhm, wait--
This seems hard.
We're friends, bro, but…
It feels…
So? Keribels?
[action music playing]
Let's do it, for Ibyang and Janine.
Bro, come on.
For the children. Let's do it.
- [Gavin] For the children.
- Come on, come on. For the children.
[others] For the children.
Whoo!
Fabulous!
Okay. Through the fire!
[shouting, cheering]
[cheering]
Waiter! One more, one more!
Another round! Another round!
[pensive music playing]
Janine…
Are you okay?
I don't want to be here anymore.
I want to go home.
Don't worry.
Tatoy will save us.
He's good at finding people and things!
What if he doesn't?
What will they do to us?
Will they torture us?
Kill us? Like that?
Don't think about that.
Just say…
[somber music playing]
Thread through the needle.
Pass through, but don't stop.
Tatoy taught me that.
All the… bad thoughts you have,
just let them pass.
Like thread through a needle.
[melodramatic music playing]
Sorry.
It's my fault we got kidnapped.
I don't blame you.
- [music fades]
- We're allies now, right?
[heavy music playing]
[in English] Okay. Shoulders, 15.
Where is Atoy?
[pensive music playing]
Ah, he's out buying fabric.
We need to sew our costumes, eh.
Your biceps. Hmm, are you Popeye?
What did you say?
[Cita] You're going to dance at the club?
Eh, this was Atoy's idea.
Hmm, we'll dance and lip-sync like…
like drugstore performers.
Ah, dra-- drag show performances.
In short, we'll glam up
and perform spectacularly.
[Emerson] Mmm-hmm.
It's not just that.
We really need to win.
Because that's the easiest way
to get invited to the island
where Janine and Ibyang were taken.
[Ame] Ahh.
How did you know they were taken there?
Yes, Emerson.
- Yes, right?
- [Cita, in English] Thirteen.
What if we win and get there?
How can we be sure the children
are still there?
Of course, we won't go without being sure.
Atoy and I already worked out
the info about that place.
[men] Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
[Emerson] Okay. Mm-hmm.
[pleasant music playing]
Argh.
- [Paldo] Thank you, Atoy.
- [Atoy] Let's go.
[Nestor] Oh! Thank you, thank you!
[muffled chatter]
[Paldo] So, what? More beer.
[Uno] All right. You?
[muffled chatter]
'Son.
Attach this to Trinity's collar,
Kalaf's assistant.
Just stick it on.
What is this?
[muffled chatter]
Listening device, a bug.
Stick it anywhere,
as long as it's near the mouth.
This is awesome, ah.
Like those Double O Seven spy gadgets, ah.
[cackles]
There. It's all up to you.
All right. I'll handle it.
[muffled chatter]
[clears throat]
[drag queen] Huh? A trip?
- [Emerson] Hi!
- Europe.
Oh, Trinity! Hi!
[in English] Can I take a selfie with you?
- Oh, sure! Okay.
- Selfie, yes!
[Emerson laughs] It's a selfie.
- [Emerson, in English] Okay, there you go.
- [Trinity] Okay.
- Okay.
- Yep. Another one, another one.
Another one! One more, one more.
Okay.
[action music playing]
- There you go, ah!
- Okay. All right!
[in English] You don't remember me?
You had me make your suit before.
[in English] Ah, no. I don't know you.
[in English] Ahh! You don't know me?
- I don't know you.
- Ah, you don't know me.
But I know you, you're Trinity!
Oh, thank you!
I'm a fan, I'm a fan.
Okay, nice. Nice outfit, huh. Okay.
Yes. Designer!
Wow! I love it!
- Okay. Thank you! All right, all right.
- Okay! You take care!
[Emerson] Bye, bye!
[drag queen] Oh, you're so famous.
[smirks]
[music fades]
[sneaky music playing]
Look at the time.
We still haven't picked up
anything important?
We'll be here until morning, eh.
[Trinity on device, in English]
Oh, wait. Excuse me.
I have to take this call.
Hello, Mr. Pullman!
He's already there.
He's there,
he's talking to someone on the phone.
Yes.
[in English] The schedule is confirmed,
and the new fees will be sent by email.
[Trinity on device, in English] Uh-huh.
The shipment is by next weekend.
On the night of Mr. Kalaf's
birthday celebration.
So, you have to come.
Yes.
[Trinity on device, in English] The usual,
the shipment will be
in transit from Velora Bay.
Yes, and the orders will be sorted there…
which are women and young children,
care of the Black Meridian
and Red Regalia.
[Trinity chuckles on device]
Okay, Mr. Pullman. Ciao!
Oh, it seems human trafficking has
long been the trade on that island, eh.
And, it's like… it's being used
as terrorist training grounds.
[Uno] Exactly.
That's why we really need
to expose that place,
to stop their illegal business.
We really need to get inside that island.
Not just for Janine and Ibyang,
but for all the children.
But, to get inside and save Ibyang…
you need to win
the drag show contest, right?
Sis, I don't feel any nerves from you,
you're all straight.
How will you do it?
What do you know
about drag show performance?
[Emerson smirks]
[sneaky music playing]
Miss, I'll handle that.
[Karla] Oh.
Wow, give!
[henchman] Eat now!
[suspicious music playing]
If I were you, just let us go!
If not, our dad will find you
and you'll be in trouble!
Stop talking, eat now!
[henchman] Hurry up!
You're so stubborn, huh!
You think I don't fight back against kids?
- What? What?!
- What, huh?! Hmph!
- No, please. No, no.
- [henchman] Huh?
- No-- no, please, no.
- Don't be stubborn, huh.
[Ibyang] No, no, please.
- What?!
- You too! You're so stubborn, huh!
[Janine] Ibyang!
- [henchman] What?
- What's going on?
Boss, she's been like this for a while.
She keeps answering back!
You're really bratty even here, huh?
- You need your tongue cut off. [grunts]
- [Janine groans]
[Janine] No! [gasps]
- We didn't do anything wrong to you!
- [Janine groans]
Why do you want to hurt us?!
Too bad!
Your parents did me wrong!
Especially your mother!
[sobs] But you're siblings!
I'm your niece!
We're family!
We should love each other!
Why do you want to hurt us?
Family isn't about being related by blood.
Your mother infuriates me.
Especially when I see you!
Especially you!
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[rousing music playing]
[intense music playing]
- Hello, ladies!
- [Atoy] Mmm-hmm.
[in English] I'm the leader, slash,
choreographer of The Glitter Bombz!
- [Emerson] Oww.
- I'm Antonia.
Oh, we are the…
‪UP NEXT
- [all] Karayom Kweens!
- [applause]
[Chiquita] Amateurs like you
will never take our crown,
and mark that on your ugly foreheads!
[exclaims]
[host] Come on!
Let's welcome to the stage…
The Karayom Kweens!
♪ One cut, and it's done ♪
♪ Fix this ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias